Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files A-E, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Amsterdam News photograph archive, 1920-2012.
8084
New York Amsterdam News.
189 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Photographs, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes photographs and related materials covering a broad range of topics, with a particular focus on day-to-day life in New York's African-American community during the 20th century.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Founded in 1909 by James H. Anderson, the New York Amsterdam News is one of the oldest African-American owned and run newspapers in the country. Initially focused on local news in New York in general and Harlem in particular, the Amsterdam News broadened its scope to include national news under the guidance of editor Dr. C.B. Powell in the 1930s. By the 1960s, the newspaper had become a major voice in the national African-American community, offering extensive coverage of the civil rights movement. Beginning in 1982, the newspaper was edited by Wilbert A. Tatum, under whose guidance the newspaper remained a voice in local and national affairs. In 1996, Tatum turned control of the newspaper over to his daughter, Elinor Tatum, who remained the publisher and editor-in-chief through the 2000s.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes photographs and related materials covering a broad range of topics, with a particular focus on day-to-day life in New York's African-American community during the 20th century. Subjects include civil rights marches and protests, church events, high school graduations, local politics, and fashion. Some photographs were taken by staff photographers, while others originated with wire services or as submissions from individuals or agencies. Formats in the collection include silver gelatin prints, negatives (including many unpublished images), contact sheets, Polaroids, wire photos, and halftone prints. As the working photo archive of a continuously-published newspaper, many of the images have retouching, attached captions, press releases, cover letters, and printer's instructions. In addition to photographs, the collection includes ephemera and manuscript material, including newspaper article drafts, typescript and mimeographed speeches, correspondence, event programs, magazine and newspaper clippings, employment applications, press releases, and newspaper production materials.
The bulk of the materials in the archive range from the mid-1940s through the mid-1990s. The materials are divided into series, reflecting the organization of the materials in the AM News offices. A major sub-series of the collection is the archive of Mel Tapley, who began working for the Amsterdam News in 1942 and served as entertainment editor until his retirement in 1997. The Mel Tapley archive includes a wide variety of material, including correspondence, manuscript and typescript articles and notes, artwork, press kits, publicity photos, and printing plates for comic strips drawn by Tapley.
Photographers represented in the collection include Bert Andrews, Kwame Brathwaite, Al Burley, James C. Campbell, Curt Clemons, Juanita M. Cole, Karl Crutchfield, L. St. Clair Dummett, Monroe S. Frederick II, James Gilbert, Dave Greene, Austin Hansen, Tex Harris, Bob Head, Cecil Layne, David McAdams, Bill Moore, Allen Morgan, Vondel Nichols, Lem Peterkin, George M. West, and Lloyd Yearwood. Photo agencies and services represented include Pictorial Enterprise, Wide World Photo, Harris Photo, News Voice International, Rapid News Photo, United Press International, Negro Press Photo Service, Wagner International Photos, and Ace Creative Photos.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York Amsterdam News.
Titles:
New York Amsterdam news.
Subjects:
African American newspapers.; African Americans -- New York (State) -- New York.
Places:
New York (N.Y.); Harlem (New York, N.Y.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Because of the size of this collection, the guide is broken up into several different pages. Each page is then further separated into different series. The majority of the sereis titles come from titles given by the Amsterdam News.
Main Guide Content Listing
Series A. Main photo sequence
The main alphabetic sequence of prints containing material from 1920-2012 with the bulk being 1944-1996.
Subject files A
Subject files B
Subject files C
Subject files D
Subject files E
Subject files F
Subject files G
Subject files H
Subject files I
Subject files J
Subject files K
Subject files L
Subject files M
Subject files N
Subject files O
Subject files P
Subject files Q
Subject files R
Subject files S
Subject files T
Subject files U
Subject files V
Subject files W
Subject files X
Subject files Y
Subject files Z
Series B. Inactive File
File of inactive, defunct, or deceased individuals and organizations. Bulk material dates from before 1980.
Series C. Presorted Photos
A roughly sorted series of photos.
Series D. Semi Alphabetized Photos
A second roughly sorted series of photos. Most date from 1980-1999.
Series E. Dated Folders
Photos from the 1990s sorted by date.
Series F. Sports Photos
Mostly promotional photos from sports teams.
Series G. Contemporary File
An alphabetic sequence of photos primarily from 1988-2000, but with some older material.
Series H. Transfer File
An alphabetic sequence of topical files with bulk material dates from the 1960s-1970s.
Series I. Dead Photo File
Photos from the 2000s organized by date of their publication in the Amsterdam News.
Series J. Loose Unsorted Items
Unsorted items found in various locations around the Amsterdam News office.
Series MT. Mel Tapley Collection
The personal archive of Mel Tapley, who began working at the Amsterdam News in 1942 and served as the entertainment editor until 1997. Includes a wide variety of ephemera, artwork, manuscript and typescript material, and correspondence.
Miscellaneous Mailings and Press Files
Mel Tapley Artwork
Unsorted Photos
Press Mailings
Books and Booklets
Press Kits
Press Releases
Oversize and Fax Press Releases
Periodicals, Newspapers, Magazines
Audio and Visual Media
CONTAINER LIST
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files A
    - A & S Cabinet Makers (Box A-1, Folder 1)
      Photographer if identified: Jerry Eaderesto
      Number of Prints: 2
    - A & T University (Box A-1, Folder 2)
      All three prints have a typescript leaf attached with a paperclip.
      Number of Prints: 3
    - The A-Remians (Box A-1, Folder 3)
      Photographer if identified: C. Elliott Braithwaite
      Number of Prints: 1
    - Aaron Loves Angela (Box A-1, Folder 4)
      Also three velox prints. One print has two attached photocopied leaves.
      Number of Prints: 14
    - Aaron, Henry "Hank" (Box A-1, Folder 5)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen Studio
    - Aaron, Walter M. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-1, Folder 6)
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photographers
    - Aaron, William (Box A-1, Folder 7)
    - Aaron, Willie (Box A-1, Folder 8)
    - Aarons, Roalk A. (Box A-1, Folder 9)
    - Aaronson, Stanley (Dr.) (Box A-1, Folder 10)
    - AARP (Box A-1, Folder 11)
    - AAU Champions (Box A-1, Folder 12)
    - Abarca, Lydia (Box A-1, Folder 13)
      Photographer if identified: Shalmon Bernstein, Martha Swope, Harris Photo
      Number of Prints: 4
    - Abbey, Leon (Box A-1, Folder 14)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix.
    - Abbey, Lincoln (Box A-1, Folder 15)
    - Abbington, Jesse (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-1, Folder 16)
    - Abbott, Cleve L. (Major) (Box A-1, Folder 17)
      With one typescript leaf attached with a paperclip.
    - Abbott, Diane (Box A-1, Folder 18)
      One print has a typescript note affixed to the verso.
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Universal Pictorial Press and Agency Ltd.
    - Abbott, Gregory (Box A-1, Folder 19)
      One print has a photocopied press release attached with a staple.
      Photographer if identified: Raul Vega
    - Abbott, Leandra (Box A-1, Folder 20)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise
      Number of Prints: 6
    - Abbott, Loretta (Box A-1, Folder 21)
      Photographer if identified: Ken Duncan
    - Abbott, Marion Stewart (Box A-1, Folder 22)
      Photographer if identified: CARE Photo
    - Abbott, Maurice (Box A-1, Folder 23)
    - Abbott, Randy (Box A-1, Folder 24)
      Also one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Andrews
    - Abbott, Robert (Rev.) (Box A-1, Folder 25)
    - Abbott, Ruth Elizabeth (Box A-1, Folder 26)
    - Abboud, Ferik I. (Box A-1, Folder 27)
      With informational pamphlet attached with a paperclip.
    - Abdel, El (Box A-1, Folder 28)
      Name on verso of print is "El Abdel Salahuddin."
    - Abdoulaye, El Hadi (Box A-1, Folder 29)
    - Abdu'l-Bahá (Box A-1, Folder 30)
      One offset-printed image.
    - Abdul (Box A-1, Folder 30)
    - Abdul, Raoul (Box A-1, Folder 31)
      Two prints have single typescript leaves attached. Folder also contains one handbill, one velox print, and two newspaper clippings.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Roy Blakey, Pictorial Enterprise
      Number of Prints: 13
    - Abdul, Roberta Eneid (Rev. Mother) (Box A-1, Folder 32)
    - Abdullah (Box A-1, Folder 33)
      One photocopied leaf adhered to verso of print.
      Photographer if identified: Motown Photo
    - Abdullah, Ahmed (Box A-1, Folder 34)
    - Abdullah, Aishah (Box A-1, Folder 35)
      One ms. leaf adhered to verso of print.
      Photographer if identified: Nikki Grimes
    - Abdur-Rahman, Kenya (Box A-1, Folder 36)
    - Abdus (Box A-1, Folder 37)
      One velox print.
    - Abdush-Shahid, Lughman (Box A-1, Folder 38)
      Photographer if identified: Bilal Farid
    - Abel, Alan (Box A-1, Folder 39)
    - Abel, Lloyd A. (Box A-1, Folder 40)
      Photographer if identified: James C. Campbell, City of New York Department of Sanitation
    - Abel, Renual N. (Box A-1, Folder 41)
    - Abel, Oneal (Box A-1, Folder 42)
      Photographer if identified: Lem Peterkin Photo
    - Abelson, Stanley (Box A-1, Folder 43)
      Two prints with carbonscript labels affixed to verso; one with photocopied leaf affixed to verso; one with newspaper clipping affixed to verso.
    - Abend, Martin (Dr.) (Box A-1, Folder 44)
      Photographer if identified: Steve Friedman
    - Abernathy, Kathy (Box A-1, Folder 45)
    - Abernathy, Laurence (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-1, Folder 46)
      Photographer if identified: Adams, Rapid News Photo
    - Abernathy, Ralph D. (Rev.) (Box A-1, Folder 47)
      Also one velox print. One print with press release stapled to border.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Jamaica Tourist Board, Gill Photographers, Carl Hampton, Elaine Tomlin, SCLC Photo, David McAdams, Citizens for Sorensen, Carmel Studios, Jersey Pictures Inc.
      Number of Prints: 30
    - Abernathy, Ralph D. (Rev.) (Box A-1, Folder 48)
      Photographer if identified: Walt Disney Productions, United Press International Photo, Wide World Photos, Monroe S. Frederick II, A. Montezuma, Harris Photo
      Number of Prints: 17
    - Abinsetts, Elaine (Box A-1, Folder 49)
    - Abner, Ewart (Box A-1, Folder 50)
      Photographer if identified: Kwame Brathwaite
    - Abner, Willoughby (Box A-1, Folder 51)
      One print has two-leaf press release attached with paperclip.
    - Abraham, Eileen (Box A-1, Folder 52)
    - Abraham, Jeanette (Box A-1, Folder 53)
    - Abraham, Nathaniel (Box A-1, Folder 54)
    - Abrahams, Andrew W. (Dr.) (Box A-1, Folder 55)
    - Abrahams, Eric (Anthony) (Box A-1, Folder 56)
      Photographer if identified: Granville Allen, Jamaica Tourist Board
    - Abrahams, Peter (Box A-1, Folder 57)
    - Abram, Morris B. (Box A-1, Folder 58)
      Photographer if identified: Paul Buiar Associates
    - Abrams, Charles (Box A-1, Folder 59)
      One print has a carbonscript press release affixed to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Walter Daran, Layne's Studio
    - Abrams, Colonel (Box A-1, Folder 60)
    - Abrams, Edgar L. (Box A-1, Folder 61)
      Staple through border of print.
    - Abrams, James E. (Box A-1, Folder 62)
    - Abrams, Richard (Box A-1, Folder 63)
      One print has a photocopied text affixed to the verso with tape.
    - Abrams, Robert (Box A-1, Folder 64)
      Also one velox print and three loose photocopied press releases (four leaves total). One print has carbonscript leaf stapled to recto. One print has carbonscript press release affixed to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Calvacca (N.Y. Post staff photographer), Scott Studio, Parkway Studios, Arnold Newman, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
      Number of Prints: 18
    - Abrams, Roz (Box A-1, Folder 65)
      Photographer if identified: Dorothy Alexander
    - Abramson, Frederick B. (Box A-1, Folder 66)
      Photographer if identified: General Services Administration Region 5
    - Abramson, Lee (Box A-1, Folder 67)
    - Abrey, Paulette (Mrs.) (Box A-1, Folder 68)
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene
    - Abu, Jimmy (Box A-1, Folder 69)
      Photographer if identified: Ronnie Brathwaite, James Gilbert
    - Abuba, Ernest (Box A-1, Folder 70)
    - Abuto, Nyanjong (Box A-1, Folder 71)
      Photographer if identified: Charles Reid
    - Abyssinian Baptist [Church] (Box A-1, Folder 72)
      One print has part of a handbill affixed to the verso with tape. One print has staple through corner of image.
      Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Bill Moore, A. Hansen, Pictorial Enterprise, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
      Number of Prints: 11
    - Abyssinian Towers (Box A-1, Folder 73)
    - Abzug, Bella (Box A-1, Folder 74)
      Also one velox print and one single-leaf photocopied press release. Two prints have single-leaf typescript press releases affixed to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Jean Wolcott, Harris Photo, Camera 1, Bob Head, United Press International
      Number of Prints: 19
    - Accidents (Box A-1, Folder 75)
      Photographer if identified: Coreen Simpson
    - Ace and the Kings (Box A-1, Folder 76)
    - Ace, Buddy (Box A-1, Folder 77)
      One print is stapled to a two-leaf mimeographed press release.
    - Ace, Johnny (Box A-1, Folder 78)
    - Ace, Richard (Box A-1, Folder 79)
      One velox print with pasted-on text.
    - Ace Spectrum (Box A-1, Folder 80)
    - Acevedo, Naomi (Box A-1, Folder 81)
    - Acevedo, Raymond (Box A-1, Folder 82)
      Photographer if identified: George West
    - Acey, Sinclair (Box A-1, Folder 83)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Acheson, Dean (Box A-1, Folder 84)
      Photographer if identified: International News Photos, Sam Schulman
    - Achille, Marcel (Box A-1, Folder 85)
      Brief typescript bio typed on verso of print.
    - Achkar, Marof (Ambassador) (Box A-1, Folder 86)
    - Acker, Jimmy (Box A-1, Folder 87)
    - Ackerman, F.W. (Box A-1, Folder 88)
      Photographer if identified: Martin-Trlak Inc.
    - Aconi, Niger (Box A-1, Folder 89)
      Photographer if identified: Pele[rhan?] Photo
    - Acorn (Members of) (Box A-1, Folder 90)
      Photographer if identified: Michael J. Henry
    - Acosta, Henry (Box A-1, Folder 91)
      Photographer if identified: Jerry Baron
    - Acosta, Viola (Box A-1, Folder 92)
      Photographer if identified: James Campbell, M. Smith
    - Acree, Donald (Box A-1, Folder 93)
      Photographer if identified: Greshoff Advertising Agency
    - Across 110th Street (Film) (Box A-1, Folder 94)
      Stills from the film, with 15-leaf mimeographed press packet.
      Number of Prints: 31
    - Across 110th Street (Film premiere) (Box A-1, Folder 95)
      Number of Prints: 8
    - Acrum, Eula (Box A-1, Folder 96)
    - Act From Under And Above (Box A-1, Folder 97)
      With photocopied press release affixed to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Bob Shamus
    - Action (Box A-1, Folder 98)
      All prints are attached (5 with paperclips, 3 with staples, 4 with tape) to computer-printed typescript press releases of varying lengths (40 leaves total).
      Photographer if identified: Emma Rivera, Peace Corps Photo
      Number of Prints: 12
    - Acuff, Eddie (Box A-1, Folder 99)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen
    - Ad Libs, The (Box A-1, Folder 100)
    - Adah Grand Chapter, OEA (Box A-1, Folder 101)
      Prints attached with staple at corner.
      Photographer if identified: Sis. N. Reese
    - Adair, Eugene (Rev.) (Box A-1, Folder 102)
      Photographer if identified: Pollard Photo, Nichols' Studio
    - Adair, Frank B. (Box A-1, Folder 103)
      Photographer if identified: Irving Kaufman, Nichols
    - Adair, Robert (Dr.) (Box A-1, Folder 104)
      Photographer if identified: Rufus Hinton, Harris Photo, Ronnie Brathwaite
    - Adair, Thelma (Box A-1, Folder 105)
      Number of Prints: 10
    - Adair, Thelma Davidson (Dr.) (Box A-1, Folder 106)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Presbyterian Office, Juanita M. Cole
      Number of Prints: 5
    - Adam & Eve (Play) (Box A-1, Folder 107)
      Photographer if identified: Kenn Duncan
    - Adam's Disciples (Box A-1, Folder 108)
      Photographer if identified: Al Burley
    - Adams, A.A. (Box A-1, Folder 109)
      Also one velox print. Photo and velox stuck together (back-to-back).
    - Adams, Ace (Box A-1, Folder 110)
    - Adams, Adelaide (Box A-1, Folder 111)
      Photographer if identified: Rapid News Photo, Nichols
    - Adams, Adele (Box A-1, Folder 112)
      Photographer if identified: Larry Mulvehill
    - Adams, Alfred (Box A-1, Folder 113)
    - Adams, Alger (Box A-1, Folder 114)
      Photographer if identified: Sally Cahur, Nichols, Rapid News Photo
    - Adams, Alton (Box A-1, Folder 115)
    - Adams, Annie (Box A-1, Folder 116)
      Photographer if identified: Teré Cuesta
    - Adams, Armenta (Box A-1, Folder 117)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert
    - Adams, Barbara (Box A-1, Folder 118)
      Photographer if identified: Allen Morgan Photo
    - Adams, Bea K. (Rev. Dr.) (Box A-1, Folder 119)
    - Adams, Betty (Box A-1, Folder 120)
    - Adams, Beverly (Box A-1, Folder 121)
    - Adams, Beverly (Intern) (Box A-1, Folder 122)
    - Adams, Billy (Box A-1, Folder 123)
      With lengthy ms. caption written on verso.
    - Adams, Bob (Box A-1, Folder 124)
      Photographer if identified: B.F. Goodrich
    - Adams, Bob (Amsterdam News) (Box A-1, Folder 125)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Price
    - Adams, Brock (Box A-1, Folder 126)
      Photographer if identified: Milton Williams
    - Adams, C. Leroy (Dr.) (Box A-1, Folder 127)
    - Adams, Calvin (Box A-1, Folder 128)
      Photographer if identified: United Press International
    - Adams, Carolyn (Box A-1, Folder 129)
      Photographer if identified: Erik Hart
    - Adams, Connie (Box A-1, Folder 130)
      Photographer if identified: Burley Photo Syndicate
    - Adams, Darryl (Box A-1, Folder 131)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Hayes
    - Adams David B. (Box A-1, Folder 132)
      Photographer if identified: Chuck Smith
    - Adams, Debbie (Box A-1, Folder 133)
      Photographer if identified: E. I. Greene, Dave Greene
    - Adams, Dolly (Box A-1, Folder 134)
    - Adams, Dolores Patricia (Miss) (Box A-1, Folder 135)
    - Adams, Don (Box A-1, Folder 136)
    - Adams, E.C. (Box A-1, Folder 137)
      Photographer if identified: Nichols
    - Adams, Edward (Box A-1, Folder 138)
      Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield
    - Adams, Edwin (Lt. Col.) (Box A-1, Folder 139)
    - Adams, Edwin B. (Box A-1, Folder 140)
      Photographer if identified: David McAdams
    - Adams, Elma (Box A-1, Folder 141)
      Two prints are attached by paperclip to a single performance program.
      Number of Prints: 7
    - Adams, Elwyn (Box A-1, Folder 142)
    - Adams, Emile (Box A-1, Folder 143)
    - Adams, Enid (Box A-1, Folder 144)
    - Adams, Eric (Box A-1, Folder 145)
    - Adams, Faye (Box A-1, Folder 146)
    - Adams, Farrell (Box A-1, Folder 147)
    - Adams, Florence (Box A-1, Folder 148)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo
    - Adams, Forrest H. (Dr.) (Box A-1, Folder 149)
    - Adams, Frederick G. (Dr.) (Box A-1, Folder 150)
      Also one velox print, one image clipped from a newspaper.
    - Adams, Gayle (Box A-1, Folder 151)
    - Adams, George D., Jr. (Box A-1, Folder 152)
    - Adams, George H. (Box A-1, Folder 153)
    - Adams, Gloria (Box A-1, Folder 154)
      Photographer if identified: United Press International Inc.
    - Adams, Harold (Box A-1, Folder 155)
      Photographer if identified: Tri-County Photo ServiceInc.
    - Adams, Jackie Rowe (Box A-1, Folder 156)
    - Adams, James E., and son Victor (Box A-1, Folder 157)
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos
    - Adams, Janis (Box A-1, Folder 158)
    - Adams, Jimmy (Box A-1, Folder 159)
      Photographer if identified: Hairston Photo, David McAdams, Burley Photo Syndicate
    - Adams, Joe (Box A-1, Folder 160)
    - Adams, Joey (Box A-1, Folder 161)
    - Adams, John (Safe Driver) (Box A-1, Folder 162)
      Photographer if identified: NYC Transit Authority
    - Adams, John H. (Box A-1, Folder 163)
      Also one single-leaf typescript press release, signed in ms. by Reginald Johnson of the National Alliance of Postal Employees. One print has staple through the border of the image.
    - Adams, John O. (Box A-1, Folder 164)
    - Adams, John Quincy (Rev.) (Box A-1, Folder 165)
      Photographer if identified: R. D. Raman
    - Adams, Julie and Julius S. (Box A-1, Folder 166)
    - Adams, Julius (Box A-1, Folder 167)
    - Adams, Laverne (Box A-1, Folder 168)
    - Adams, Leon (Box A-1, Folder 169)
    - Adams, Levi C. (Box A-1, Folder 170)
      Photographer if identified: John Foraste, Brown News Bureau
    - Adams, M.L. (Lt. Col.) (Box A-1, Folder 171)
    - Adams, Marguerita (Mrs.) (Box A-1, Folder 172)
    - Adams, Mary Jean (Box A-1, Folder 173)
      Photographer if identified: Carroll Aument
    - Adams, Matthew (Box A-1, Folder 174)
    - Adams, Natalee (Box A-1, Folder 175)
    - Adams, Nate (Box A-1, Folder 176)
    - Adams, Oleta (Box A-1, Folder 177)
    - Adams, Patrick (Box A-1, Folder 178)
      Photographer if identified: Ian Knight, Joba Associates Ltd.
    - Adams, Peter (Box A-1, Folder 179)
    - Adams, Philipp (Box A-1, Folder 180)
    - Adams, Rebecca (Box A-1, Folder 181)
      Photographer if identified: Herbert Bennett
    - Adams (Rev.) (Box A-1, Folder 182)
    - Adams, Robert (Box A-1, Folder 183)
    - Adams, Roderick (Rev.) (Box A-1, Folder 184)
    - Adams, Ron (Box A-1, Folder 185)
    - Adams, Roy H. (Box A-1, Folder 186)
      With carbonscript biography affixed to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Ernestine McClendon
    - Adams, Samuel C. (Dr.) (Box A-1, Folder 187)
    - Adams, Sterling (Box A-1, Folder 188)
    - Adams, Sylvester (Soapy) (Box A-1, Folder 189)
    - Adams, T. Gordon (Box A-1, Folder 190)
    - Adams, Tan (Box A-1, Folder 191)
      Photographer if identified: Lichtman
    - Adams, Theodore (Box A-1, Folder 192)
    - Adams, Thomas (Box A-1, Folder 193)
      Photographer if identified: Camera Arts Studio
    - Adams, Valarie (Box A-1, Folder 194)
    - Adams, Vera (Box A-1, Folder 195)
    - Adams, Wilhelmina (Box A-1, Folder 196)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, David McAdams,
    - Adat Beyt Mosheh Chorus (Box A-1, Folder 197)
    - ADC Band (Box A-1, Folder 198)
    - Addabbo, Joseph P. (Box A-1, Folder 199)
      Note on folder: "see Lommier, Harper." Four staples through border of one print.
      Photographer if identified: David Adderley, Wilson, Ralph Cooper, Edward R. Chew
    - Addabbo, Craig (Box A-1, Folder 200)
    - Adderley, A. F. (Box A-1, Folder 201)